"Kian's B&B."
I feel like I'm in a fairy tale.
This is incredible.
DEX IS HERE
Want to go sledding?
MEANWHILE
It looked fun.
-Let's go sledding.
-That sounds fun.
Want to go skating?
-We can skate for real?
-We can.
KIAN'S B&B
KIAN GOES OUT FIRST
AND THE REST FOLLOW
Let's go
Let's go sledding
ALL AT ONCE
They're doing something over there.
HAPPY
He's adorable.
They're sledding.
How am I supposed to join them?
COVERING HIS FACE WITH AN UMBRELLA
HE APPROACHES WALKING SIDEWAYS
I don't think they recognize me yet.
TOO PREOCCUPIED WITH SLEDDING
He went far.
NOW HE'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF THEM
Hello! I'm here to work part-time!
Hello!
PART-TIME WORKER DEX
-What? No way.
-I don't believe it.
A PART-TIME WORKER IS HERE?
GENUINELY SURPRISED
Hello.
I was happy. We'd gotten so many guests,
so we really needed a part-time worker.
And then Dex came,
and he's such a good worker.
-Hello, nice to meet you.
-Hello.
-Hello, it's been a while.
-Hello, Jun-ho.
TIGHT EMBRACE
He's Dex.
He was in The Iron Squad,
and I loved UDT stuff as a kid.
DEX HAS COME TO WORK
Did you know about this, Boss?
I kind of knew.
Come on.
I didn't think he'd make it.
We were physically and mentally exhausted.
He came at the right time.
He was like rain
in the midst of a drought.
Seeing you here, I feel so reassured.
You can leave it to me.
DEX IS BACKING UP HIS ALLY KIAN
I'll do my best to pull my weight here.
-He's such a good worker.
-Isn't he a good worker?
-How many days is your stay?
-It's a short stay.
A SHORT STAY?
Just until the next night.
-The next night?
-It's short-term.
Until tomorrow night?
But that's way too short!
Isn't it better not to take him?
REJECTS PART-TIMER
What are you talking about?
Isn't it better not to hire him?
Don't be like that.
I'm a short-term part-time worker.
-But just a day is such a shame.
-I know.
Let's go in and show him around.
-Yes, show me around.
-Come on in.
Gosh, what is this?
-Is this a door?
-Yes.
DOOR
What on earth?
I'm sure you can open this in one go.
How do you…
There you go!
It's easy for him.
I knew it.
HE FLIES UP AND OPENS IT IN ONE GO
He's different.
What did you just do?
-You really open the door like this?
-Yes.
Gosh, he got up so high.
No one's grabbed on
with both hands before.
What on earth? Do we close it like this?
I'll hold this. You pull the handle.
Pull! One.
-It's closed.
-What is this?
HE EASILY CLOSES IT TOO
What is this place?
It looks like a giant's…
-I feel like I've become tiny.
-It's exactly that.
That's the theme.
What is this place? It's incredible.
-Can I go up on the sofa?
-Of course.
LEAPS UP
AMAZED
SWINGING HIS FEET
It's like a studio apartment.
And we made it huge.
Right, it is a studio apartment.
People like staying in large rooms
when they're on trips.
So I thought, "Let's make the room big."
And I decided to make one really big room.
How did you think of this?
It's so like you.
That's the kitchen.
Let's go up.
How do you get up there?
By climbing this?
Yeah, you can climb up the dishrag.
Because it's the kitchen?
EASILY
This is incredible.
Nothing's easy here.
Isn't this the sink, Kian?
We made it into a jacuzzi.
Gosh, this is so tough.
Kian, this place is incredible.
The guests will use
the jacuzzi here later.
Is this really a jacuzzi?
I thought it was the sink.
FILLING IT WITH WATER
-It really is a jacuzzi.
-This is so interesting.
It's original.
-It is?
-It's so original.
Really?
It's full of surprises.
I thought it looked ordinary
from the outside.
But after coming inside,
I understand it now.
Kian, you have something on your face.
I'm so tired.
You really do look tired.
I feel like my body's breaking down.
Really? All right.
Don't worry, Kian. Just leave it to me.
PATTING
Thanks, man.
I can see
you're doing everything for real.
We seriously need you right now.
You cook for them too?
-Just one meal at dinner.
-One meal?
What time are you leaving tomorrow?
Make dinner before you go.
Make dinner tomorrow.
GIVING HIM WORK
I'm sure they'll be curious
about your cooking.
Are there many ingredients?
Wait, is this a fridge?
It is.
Geez.
Kian, I want to take this home.
Okay.
I should figure out
where everything is first.
WHILE DEX EXPLORES KITCHEN
THE SKATING GROUP
Be careful.
-Are you okay?
THE SLEDDING GROUP
THEY'RE ALL ENJOYING THE SNOW
That was good.
You're cold, aren't you?
-Want to go in?
-Yes.
-Let's stomp the snow off.
-Okay.
SLEDDING GROUP RETURNS
-It was fun, right?
-Yes.
-It was so fun.
-Wasn't sledding awesome?
-Should we head in?
-Yes.
SKATING GROUP RETURNS TOO
SCREECH
-Please open the door!
IS ANYONE HOME?
Maybe they can't hear us?
Please open the door for us!
They want us to open the door.
THE PART-TIMER GOES TO HELP
You need help with the door?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Goodness, Dex. I'm so glad you came.
It's one of the guests who came yesterday.
THE SKATING GROUP HASN'T SEEN DEX YET
-Welcome back.
-Thank you.
-Hello. Come on in.
STARING
Come on in.
What?
I'm a part-time worker.
I'm Dex. Come on in.
I was so surprised.
I was just so surprised.
Hello.
When did you come?
Just now.
Just now?
I had no idea.
I thought he was just a guest.
I didn't expect it at all.
JUST AMAZED
-Did you see our part-timer?
-I did.
But you're only here for a day,
so I'm bummed.
Yeon-koung, I'll do all the work today.
The mood's changed a bit.
-Is it time for dinner now?
-Yes.
-Are these the only dishes?
-Dishes?
TONIGHT'S DINNER
KIMCHI JJIGAE
AND POTATO STIR-FRY
I'll make something.
Let me see.
THE PART-TIME WORKER WANTS
TO MAKE OTHER SIDE DISHES
Dex, do you need help?
No, I'm good.
-You're good?
-Yes, get some rest.
All right.
Can you cook?
Of course. I've been living
by myself for ten years.
I can whip something up in no time.
Maybe some fried eggs.
ADDITIONAL SIDE DISH
FRIED EGGS
To those who live on their own,
time is priceless.
The key is it that
needs to be easy and simple.
SIMPLEST DISH TO MAKE
You know, fried eggs and ketchup
are good enough side dishes.
DONE IN 10 MINUTES
PUTTING A LID ON
Let's cover this up.
We can't have dust getting in.
HE KEEPS THINGS CLEAN TOO
AND NEXT
I just need to cook the mushrooms now.
STIR-FRYING VARIOUS VEGETABLES
Gosh, you make things in no time.
I'm just adding more options.
This should be enough.
STIR-FRY IS DONE IN 6 MINUTES
ADDITIONAL SIDE DISH 2
MUSHROOM AND VEGGIE STIR-FRY
I mixed hot pepper sauce tuna
with kimchi tuna.
LAST SIDE DISH
-It's all done.
-All right.
I don't like food that has cooled down.
-So…
-You're wrapping it up?
HE WRAPS IT IN FOIL
THOROUGHLY
It's hot since I covered it up nicely.
This is so we can serve good food.
DEX'S 3 ADDITIONAL SIDE DISHES
This will keep them warm.
This should be good enough.
Thanks.
KIAN'S GUARDIAN
SLAP
It's A-rin and the others.
Why is a guest trying to open it?
6:05 P.M.
-Hello.
A-JIN, A-RIN, IN-BEOM, JUN-YEOP RETURN
Welcome back.
Hey, A-rin and A-jin.
-We're back.
-Hi.
You bundled up a bit more today.
-That's right.
-Yeah.
Good.
JUN-YEOP STARES AT THE KITCHEN
THREE EMPLOYEES ON THE FLOOR
NEXT TO KIAN
THERE'S SOMEONE UNFAMILIAR
I don't believe this.
Dex is here.
-For real?
-It's Dex!
Seriously?
His wolf-like and sexy side profile.
I knew it was Dex.
-Did you see him?
-What?
Dex's there.
-What? You're lying.
His sharp nose.
It really was Dex.
Seriously, I can't believe this.
They're going crazy.
Dex.
-Yes?
-The guests who just came back…
It's really him?
They're going crazy because of you.
Really? Where are they?
Hello.
-Hello.
SEEING DEX IN REAL LIFE
Geez, you all acted so different
when you first saw me.
I feel so hurt.
My goodness.
-No, we've been…
-No.
SUDDEN AFFECTION
What was that? He suddenly did this to me.
I know.
-I'm hurt.
-All of a sudden?
It's not what you think.
We were in awe then too.
We have to…
bring the food down.
-Can you try bringing the stew down?
-The stew?
There's a basket up there.
THE BOSS'S PULLEY
-This?
-Yeah.
Bring this down in here?
LOWER THE STEW WITH THE BASKET?
Where do I even begin? It doesn't fit.
We should find a way
to conveniently send things up and down.
-I'll sort this out, Kian.
-Okay.
I'll make a new mode of transport.
HE BREAKS THE EXISTING PULLEY DOWN FIRST
FINDS SOME ROPE
AND A SMALL TABLE
He's quite resourceful.
He used to be in the UDT.
That's why.
I'll try to make something good.
HE TIES THE ROPE TO THE TABLE LEG
TO ANOTHER LEG
TO THE THIRD LEG
AND TO THE LAST LEG
THE UPGRADED PULLEY LOOKS GOOD
-He tied it up well.
-He's good.
Let's give it a try.
The food's coming down.
-It's coming?
-Let's go get it.
Like this? It is pretty stable.
STABLE
-Like this?
-Good.
-Is it okay?
-Incredible.
Good. We got it.
JJIGAE IS DELIVERED SAFELY
That was really stable.
Very nice.
I'm relieved.
THE BOSS TRIES IT HIMSELF TOO
ADDITIONAL SIDE DISHES COME DOWN
Good.
-Thank you. What's this?
-What's inside?
-It's heavy.
-What is it?
They're side dishes.
Simple ones.
They do make it look
like a generous spread.
REHEATING JUN-HO'S KIMCHI JJIGAE
-Kian, let me clean up here quickly.
-Okay.
I'll just give this a wipe down.
It's so messy. I can't just leave it.
HE PUTS AWAY SAUCES HE USED
TIDYING UP
CONTINUOUSLY
All done.
CLEAN
It's clean now.
This is insane.
6:30 P.M.
They're back.
-They're back.
-Welcome back.
-Sorry.
ICE CLIMBERS ARE BACK
EVERYONE'S BACK
Everyone, after dinner,
you can use the jacuzzi or sauna.
After that, we'll open the karaoke room.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
Today's main chef was Jun-ho.
We used all the ingredients
we had left over
and made kimchi jjigae,
potato and Spam stir-fry.
And I made some other side dishes.
-Gosh, they look good.
-There's tuna.
There's mushroom and vegetable stir-fry.
-And fried eggs, which everyone likes.
-Fried eggs.
Please enjoy.
-Bon appétit.
-It's self-serve.
You can take
as much as you want on your trays.
Eat up.
This is your last meal as civilians.
Why does it look like army food though?
-Thank you for the food.
-Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
I didn't know how it would taste,
but it was so good.
So I just devoured it.
DEVOURING
This is good.
The spicy food made me feel
nice and warm inside.
I enjoyed the kimchi jjigae the most.
You'll be eating in the military
around this time tomorrow.
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
-That's crazy.
-It is.
How sad.
FINISHING ALL THEIR FOOD
-It's nice to see you eating so well.
-Thank you.
By the way, are you an athlete?
We're PE majors.
To become PE teachers?
Because of your clothes, I thought…
I know.
I thought you were athletes.
I often hear that I resemble
Ms. Kim Yeon-koung.
Really?
ME?
LET ME SEE
I can see it.
SHE RESEMBLES YEON-KOUNG
-Really?
-Yes.
Everyone finished all of their food.
That's so great.
CLEANUP TIME
Push the trays this way.
This looks delicious.
WHILE CLEANING UP FOOD WASTE
LEFTOVER JJIGAE
SITS DOWN PROPERLY
-Kian.
-Am I acting like a beggar?
What do you mean?
You've always been like this.
ALREADY USED TO IT
-We almost ate all of it.
-Right.
COLLECT FOOD WASTE IN POT
These are the fewest leftovers so far.
THE FEWEST LEFTOVERS IN THE PAST 7 DAYS
The jjigae was so good.
Come, now.
You've been working nonstop
since you arrived.
Right. I feel bad.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm totally fine.
HE GOES TO THE KITCHEN FIRST
I should go up and bring it down.
HE LOWERS THE PULLEY QUIETLY
It's here.
It came down quietly.
Let's move each of these up.
RETURNING UTENSILS
-Why did you put the kitchen up here?
-What?
-That's usually where the kitchen goes.
-But…
Nice.
Good.
It was easy since you lifted it up high.
GREAT TEAMWORK
AFTER A SATISFYING DINNER
That was so delicious.
CHECKING WATER IN THE JACUZZI
Everyone, the jacuzzi water will get cold.
Go up if you want to use it.
Or you can use the sauna.
At 7:30 p.m.,
they'll be open for about an hour.
JACUZZI AND SAUNA ARE BOTH OPEN
SAUNA ON THE 1ST FLOOR
Did you wash up first?
JACUZZI ON THE 2ND FLOOR
It's so warm.
GUESTS ENTER
I feel like a fish in a bathtub.
This was Boss's ambitious creation.
-Right. It is warm.
-It's warm.
YEON-KOUNG JOINS
JACUZZI IS GETTING CROWDED
OUTSIDE THE WINDOW
It's snowing outside too.
WITH HEAVY SNOW
We should turn on some Christmas carols.
This is so romantic.
WHILE THEY ENJOY A ROMANTIC WINTER
Isn't the snow incredible?
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
Hey, In-beom.
Should we cut your hair now?
Would it be too cold outside?
It's not that cold.
Let's cut it all off outside.
-Let's do that.
-Okay.
-It'll get messy here.
-Exactly.
Let's go, Dex.
-He's shaving his hair today?
-Yes.
He's grown it for two years.
The time has come.
DAY BEFORE ENLISTMENT
THE TIME HAS COME
A plastic bag.
Do you have scissors?
Yes, I have them.
KIAN'S B&B
Gosh, look at the swirling snow.
IN THE SWIRLING SNOW
It's snowing more than earlier.
Hey, let's do it over there.
We can cut your hair in Waterville.
IT'S WINTERVILLE, NOT WATERVILLE
How about in here? What do you think?
-Let's do it in the center.
-Right.
IN THE SKATING RINK BARBERSHOP
You go first.
SHAVING OUTSIDE
I'll go first.
-Be careful when you take this off.
-Okay.
A PLASTIC BAG FOR A GOWN
Hold it here so hair doesn't get in.
Sit down.
MIXED FEELINGS
Sit.
SUPER NERVOUS
It feels weird to cut someone else's hair.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
-This way.
-Let's do it.
He's grown this for two years.
HAIR HE'S GROWN FOR 2 YEARS
SHAKING
I'll cut it, okay?
This feels strange.
-Here I go.
-Okay!
It's being cut.
Hey, look.
Hey, look at this.
Gosh, it's… Take a look at this.
This was your hair.
You're handsome, so you're still fine.
-Does it hurt?
-No, I'm okay.
Oh, my goodness.
Hey, this is an honor.
Is it okay for me to touch this hair?
To cut the hair you've grown out…
-The honor's mine.
-Thank you for this chance.
The day I left home
-Boarded the train
-And went to boot camp
I'll use the clippers now.
-Okay.
-What guard size is this?
It's 12 mm.
All right.
We're in the fast lane now.
Go bold.
-I'll start in the middle.
-Okay.
It's being cut.
I can't believe I'm getting
a buzz cut to become a baldy.
-Are you distressed?
-He is.
-He must be.
-Yeah, it's indescribable.
CLOSING HIS EYES
This feeling.
We've been there too.
It feels like you're going somewhere
-beyond the point of return.
-Right.
They all say it'll pass soon,
but the fact is,
time passes so slowly in there.
It feels really long.
BRUTALLY HONEST CONSOLING
Around this time tomorrow,
you'll have your first roll call.
-I'll have fun tonight before I go.
-You should.
But this will be
such an unforgettable memory.
-You'll remember it forever.
-Yeah, totally.
You came to Kian's B&B
the day before enlistment
and got your hair shaved
out in heavy snow.
A STRANGE BARBERSHOP
I feel really strange too.
HE BECOMES SENTIMENTAL TOO
SO SENTIMENTAL
-Are you getting choked up?
-I am.
You were going to enter together,
but you can't,
so you must feel bad.
It's almost finished.
-It looks cool.
-I bet you're curious.
-Yes.
-It looks cool.
We should hold up
a mirror for our customer.
How is it? I bet it's been ages
since you've seen your hair so short.
You don't remember, right?
I don't.
I buzzed it very neatly.
-Nice.
-Thank you.
IN-BEOM'S HEAD HAS BEEN SHAVED
Let me see. It looks good.
He looks even more handsome.
This is better.
-This is better?
-It is.
-Because you're handsome.
-Yeah.
I'll make a safe return from the military.
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
Salute!
VERY SATISFIED BARBER
He's a soldier already.
-Please cut my hair too.
-Yes, let's cut yours too.
Our second customer.
We will begin the shaving ceremony.
Right away.
What on earth?
A BIG WAD OF HAIR
Maybe since it's your second time,
you're not hesitating at all.
WITHOUT HESITATION
Maybe like this? Let me see.
Come on, hurry up and cut it nicely.
You have to do this first though.
Right, a shave down the middle.
First, a shave down the middle.
Gosh, what is this feeling?
This feels so strange.
-All done.
-It was cut nicely.
-Okay.
-Well done.
JUN-YEOP HAS BEEN SHAVED TOO
I'll make sure to come back
safe and sound too.
I hope you two take care as you serve.
But how do you feel?
Your friend did this together for you.
You…
Why did you do it?
Hey.
If you think about it,
he was being a loyal friend.
LOYAL BUZZ CUT DUO
So we shaved…
We shaved our heads.
I couldn't let my friend do it alone.
For the remaining month,
I was going to think of it
as being in the army,
so I cut my hair with him.
I'm touched that he'd go that far for me.
They wished me good luck in the military.
It was very heartwarming.
Okay.
You look good though.
You look good too.
My hair.
HAIR AS A MEMENTO
Keep it with you.
The back of their heads!
That's a familiar sight.
Hey, now that they've cut their hair,
it feels so real.
I think I've always seen life
from my own perspective.
"This is how soldiers feel."
But this time, it went beyond that.
They're young enough to be my nephews.
I cut their hair as an elder,
so it felt a bit strange.
This was actually made
to be a skating rink.
-This spot?
-Yeah.
-Gosh.
-Now, it feels like a barbershop.
BARBERSHOP IS CLOSED
They must've cut their hair.
They shaved their heads.
-Did they shave their heads?
-They did.
It looks good on you.
Hey, it looks good on you.
Okay.
You look cool.
-You look handsome.
-Thank you.
They both cut their hair.
-Mr. Kian, I'll take the clippers.
-Okay.
-I'll clean them.
THEY CHECK THEIR APPEARANCES
Does it feel different
because I cut it for you?
-Of course.
-Really?
-It means a lot to us.
-Right.
It's not bad?
IT'S NOT BAD
They said it's okay.
FEELING PROUD
A SELFIE TO COMMEMORATE
MEANWHILE
What was your major again?
I'm a nursing major.
Are you preparing to look for jobs now?
No, I'm running a small YouTube channel.
LEE SU-RYEON
NURSING MAJOR, YOUTUBER
I'm a college student too.
What?
I'm a PE major
at Korea National Open University.
I enrolled in 2024.
We enrolled in 2024 too.
HEY, FELLOW STUDENT
-You're attending college right now?
-Yes.
Do you have the time?
I take classes online.
-So you're going to be juniors?
-Yes.
I'm going to be a junior too.
But my grades were bad last semester,
so I'm not sure
if I'll be able to graduate, but…
WORRIED ABOUT HER GRADES
You're living life to the fullest.
Goodness.
Everyone seems happy.
They become close
and get sad when they leave.
Really? Has anyone ever cried?
I almost cried.
-You did?
-You know, on their last days…
-You become attached very quickly here.
-Right.
This room makes that possible
because it brings people together.
I think so too.
Guests want to interact with us.
-Right.
-And the others are so good with that.
Yeon-koung's especially good.
Maybe it's because she's older.
Yeah, she's very easy to approach.
My little sister.
My older sister.
I guess I should accept
that we look alike.
My little sister.
Zuha's good too.
She does a good job.
Jun-ho too.
TALKING ABOUT ANIMALS
I'm the worst one at interacting.
-But you have your own way.
-Right.
I can't bother to get changed,
so I'll just go in.
Welcome. Isn't this the best?
JOINS TO INTERACT
I love it.
I should sweat it out a bit here.
This is so nice.
I should get some rest.
PART-TIME WORKER TAKES A REST
Let's go to the sauna.
This is so fun.
You can take your time.
EXODUS FROM THE JACUZZI
Hello.
I'm back.
A FULL SAUNA
Everyone ends up here.
MAKING IT HOTTER
IT'S GETTING HOTTER
See the sweat?
-I feel it.
-Me too.
-Want to go run with our shirts off?
-What?
-Want to go? Let's go.
-Yes.
THEY SUDDENLY GO OUT?
Let's face the cold.
In our bare feet?
-Let's go.
Let's go!
SU-RYEON JOINS TOO
LATE-NIGHT SNOWBALL FIGHT
Take off your shirts.
COOLING DOWN SAUNA HEAT WITH SNOW
It's so cold!
It was something I did dream of doing.
I loved that the most.
It's so cold!
THE BOSS IS CAPTURED
It's so cold.
RUNNING AWAY
Should we go too?
ZUHA AND CHOI SISTERS JOIN TOO
It's cold!
It was so fun. It was so romantic.
It's so cold!
Gosh, it's cold.
STRAIGHT BACK INTO THE SAUNA
Amazing.
Incredible.
THEY ENJOY GOING
BETWEEN HOT AND COLD AREAS
This is pretty fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
He threw snow at my mouth.
-I made a snowball right away.
-It went down your throat?
Really?
THE BOSS GETS OUT
I'm so hot.
HE PUTS BACK ON CLOTHES HE TOOK OFF
AND RESTS IN THAT STATE
Isn't this so nice?
EVEN AFTER THAT
"Control yourself."
"I'm going to tell my boyfriend."
THEY BECOME CLOSER IN THE SAUNA
It's Squid Game.
-In Squid Game?
-Yes.
8:30 P.M.
Should I have some beer?
Hey, those…
Hold on.
They must be frozen.
-What?
-It's been a while.
-The ones outside?
Yeah, the beer.
-There's beer outside?
-Yeah.
Push me.
Let's go.
Where are they?
Gosh, look at this.
Is this it? These are beers?
The snow's piled up.
BEER WAS KEPT IN SNOW
-My feet are so cold.
-It's so cold.
Let's have some cold beer.
LATE NIGHT SNACK TIME
-Come over here.
-Okay.
-Hey, over here.
-Come sit with us.
Bring some soda.
THE KIDS BRING SODA
THEY TALK IN SMALL GROUPS
How do you feel? It's your last night.
I don't want to go.
THE FOUR CHECK OUT TOMORROW
Did you talk much with the staff?
-With Zuha.
-We talked a lot with her.
-We were basically stuck on her.
-Really?
Yes, we talked a lot.
I did see you
interact with female guests a lot.
-Right. It was fun.
-She was the best.
We'll never get to have
this kind of experience again.
-I've been so happy.
-Right.
That's so good to hear.
RELIEVED
Right.
HE TAKES OFF HIS WATCH
-You bought one, right?
-Yes.
You're entering in April?
A SOLDIER'S MUST-HAVE ITEM
Oh, my.
-A watch-giving ceremony.
-It's nothing fancy.
Still.
WATCH-AWARDING CEREMONY
That's awesome.
Hey. We're pretty cool, aren't we?
We cut your hair and gave you a watch.
I quite liked that watch too.
I'm sure the battery
will last a long time.
So it'll last until you finish
your military service.
-Thank you.
-Don't lose it.
-I'll never lose it.
-Good.
Anyway, it felt strange
when I was cutting your hair.
Really?
It felt so strange. It was just…
It felt weird for some reason.
It reminded me a little bit
of my younger self
and made me think
about how much time has passed.
And I know it'll be tough
for you in many ways.
I have no watch now.
Hey, I'll give it to you when you leave.
I still need it.
-Tell me when you leave.
-Okay.
-I'm not taking it back.
-Right.
TAKING IT BACK
He took it back.
He had it taken away.
I still really need it.
CHECKING TIME FOR KARAOKE
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
When I go in tomorrow,
I'm sure I'll miss this place a lot.
What are you going to do once he leaves?
You'll be so lonely.
We go way back. We've gone to
all the same schools together.
He's my good friend. My dearest friend.
STARING
I think he really likes him a lot.
-Jun-yeop likes In-beom?
-One-sided?
-He likes him more.
-Really?
And he doesn't show it.
But he likes his friend too on the inside.
That's why they're friends.
And Mr. Kian said
he also had a friend like him.
EMOTIONALLY INVESTED
Let me give you
the watch again before I forget.
I'll just look at my phone
to check the time.
HE PUTS IT ON HIM AGAIN
What are you high schoolers
interested in these days?
-Everyone's into K-pop idols.
-Right.
I heard Yun-woo's phone wallpaper
was a photo of Kazuha.
-That's right.
-Really?
And Seong-bhin's was a photo of me.
Would you like to see it?
Really?
Seong-bhin, please. Don't.
GOSH, PUT IT AWAY
Give it to me.
What?
Seong-bhin, I told you not to do this.
Jun-ho.
I can't believe you.
-Is that Yeon-koung?
-Yeah, it's me.
-When I don't want to study…
-You use it?
A GOOD STIMULUS FOR STUDYING
Once, I read Cosmos,
and my brain became all jumbled.
-But space really was interesting.
-Right.
I mean, we as humans
struggle so hard to survive.
Right.
Then, when I became aware of
the universe or stars, it suddenly felt…
Right.
-Everything felt so insignificant.
-Insignificant.
THEY STRONGLY AGREE
The vast universe.
Sometimes, it makes me feel at peace.
What I thought about recently
was this one sentence in the book
about larger clusters existing
beyond our solar system.
After I saw that,
I talked about it with my mom.
By the way,
what do your parents do for work?
They're not in the science field.
I just talk with them about space.
Still, they need to have
some knowledge about it to talk with you.
I think they like science programs.
Really? Did they grow
to like them because of you?
Or have they always liked those shows?
They became interested because of me
and started watching them more.
They see and ask me about things
from those shows that I don't know.
My case is similar.
When I was active in Japan,
my parents wanted to share interests
with me, so they studied Japanese.
Really?
So, that helped us communicate.
And sometimes, I'd even talk
in Japanese with my mom.
If your parents hadn't always done that,
it means they studied it just for you.
-I'm grateful.
-You should be.
-They're such good parents.
-You think so?
KIAN'S B&B
Boss.
Didn't you say you'd be the host?
Are we starting?
Okay. Then, shall we get ready?
All right.
-Mr. Kian!
-Let's go!
HE GOES TO DRESS UP FOR KARAOKE
FINISHED CHANGING
What?
He's dressed up. Oh, my gosh.
HIS SUIT CATCHES THEIR ATTENTION
The host.
-This is going to be so fun.
-Our host, Kian.
9:00 P.M.
KARAOKE ROOM IS OPEN
-Okay.
-How are you, everyone?
We have just two days left now
at Kian's B&B.
KIAN'S B&B CLOSES IN 2 DAYS
-Two days left.
-I'm so sad.
Anyway, I'd been thinking all day
about how to make things fun for you
during your stay.
It's hard. It always is,
but I'm doing my best.
So…
I hope you enjoy your stay!
-Okay!
We're going to perform a duet.
WITH WHO?
ME!
SETTING THE STAGE
Shall we get started? Right away?
NERVOUS
Here we go.
WHAT WILL BE THE FIRST PERFORMANCE?
Oh, my.
JUST HEARING THE INTRO MAKES HIM TEAR UP
-Oh, no.
-Gosh, he's going to cry.
It seems they're singing it for you guys.
"A LETTER FROM A PRIVATE"
BY KIM KWANG-SEOK
-They're going in.
-This is dedicated to our two young men.
The day I left home
Boarded the train
And went to boot camp
After I bowed deeply to my parents
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
And walked out the front gate
Take care, In-beom.
-Stay safe.
-Take care.
-Take care of yourself.
-Good luck in April.
My hair…
-After it was cut short
-Looked funny at first
-But my smile
-In the mirror
-Falls along with my heart
-If I go up on the nearby hill
-Will I be able to see my town?
GETTING CHOKED UP
Now, it's time to start again
The dreams of my youth
I'm getting choked up.
Since it's our last night tonight,
we picked this song.
IN-BEOM AND JUN-YEOP'S RESPONSE
TO FIRST SONG
"After This Night"!
"AFTER THIS NIGHT"
BY YIM JAE-BEUM
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
On this night full of lights
A sad farewell is approaching
But I still have a lot of things
I want to say
After this night passes
We'll have to part ways once again
-What on earth? He's good.
-Yeah, In-beom's a good singer.
Without even saying a word like this
Like this!
Do I have to let you go?
EXPLOSION OF EMOTIONS
-He's so different when singing.
-Incredible!
Good luck in the military!
Salute! Good luck!
That was an awesome performance.
Did you prepare anything?
She can do some cheerleading.
I want to see her be a cheerleader.
-Cheerleading.
SHE GOES TO SHOW HER CHEERLEADING
She didn't hesitate.
"HIGHWAY IN THE GALE"
BY YU JUNG-SEOK
Give me one more gale of courage
CHEERING WITH KARAOKE WIGS
So I won't succumb to the rough waves
Look at how she's moving her body.
Hope to leave a new mark on the vast land
I'll hold onto it and run to you
All together now!
Give me one more gale of courage
UP AND DOWN
So I won't succumb…
A WAVE WITH ARMS AROUND SHOULDERS
ENTHUSIASTIC
Hope to leave a new mark on the vast land
IN A TRANCE
I'll hold onto it and run to you
To you
Thank you.
Nice!
That was great!
-Let's go, A-rin and A-jin.
-Here they finally come.
Finally.
A-rin and A-jin.
I wonder what they'll sing.
What on earth?
You're so cute! You look so cute!
-What?
-What is this?
This song?
DANCING FURIOUSLY
SHOCKED
They're suddenly so hyper.
A DAZZLING PERFORMANCE
Very nice!
Get up!
-Get up.
-Get up!
Everyone's out of their mind
Everyone!
They're all going crazy
Who can I trust? How can I?
I can't trust them anymore
Yeah, that's right!
Don't trust anyone!
You and everyone else
in this world are shallow
Change, change, change it!
Change everything!
Change, change, change all of it!
Change, change, change the lies!
Change, change, change the whole world!
A-rin and A-jin, you crushed it!
You crushed it!
-This is what I'm talking about!
-This is awesome!
A DOPAMINE RUSH
Make some noise!
IT'S NOT OVER YET
JUMPING UP AND DOWN
You're amazing!
-He's so cute.
-He looks like a squirrel.
THE KARAOKE ROOM
IS IN A FRENZY
THE BOSS IS IN A FRENZY
KIAN'S B&B IS HEATING UP
They're so excited.
They pretty much all know how to have fun.
Especially today.
-They're mostly singing upbeat songs.
-Right.
Well, Boss? Are you satisfied?
-I'm so happy.
-Right?
I'm so happy.
He says he's so happy.
Happy? He's happy today?
-That's a relief.
-It is.
HAPPY
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
Are you going to bed now?
Yeah, I am.
Let's brush our teeth.
THE HIGH SCHOOLERS GO TO BED FIRST
Listen. They're still high schoolers,
so they have to go to bed.
I think we should
let them sleep in a room.
-Sure.
-Of course.
MORE THAN HAPPY TO
THANKS TO THE GIRLS
-This is nice and cozy.
-I know.
THEY CAN SLEEP COMFORTABLY
10:00 P.M.
I have a question.
You made some insane comments
on Single's Inferno.
Like in a good way.
Did you really come up
with those comments on your own?
I just said those things
when I was feeling extremely shy,
but people liked that.
So, I was pretty surprised.
The time when you grabbed the flag,
that was so…
I really liked the swimming pool scene.
Shall I do it for you?
HATES IT
Hold on!
FAINTING
She was so overwhelmed that she fainted.
I was so happy.
She's loving it.
I'm grateful you came.
MEANWHILE
And for letting me cut
the hair you'd grown for two years,
thank you so much.
-You look cool with a buzz cut.
-I'm so grateful.
What time do you enter boot camp?
-At 2:00 p.m.
-At 2:00 p.m.?
The countdown begins.
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
I don't know
if we'll cross paths in the future,
but I hope we do in someplace cool.
Let's all do our best.
Cheers.
We should go to bed.
Everyone, you can just
leave things there and go to bed.
Go to bed. We'll clean it up tomorrow.
Hey, Jun-yeop and In-beom.
Yes?
I heard you're leaving early
in the morning. This is my book.
YEON-KOUNG SAYS GOODBYE WITH GIFTS
-Thank you.
-Give it a read.
I will.
-Good luck.
-In the military…
Okay, I'll root for you.
Take care.
-Thank you.
-All right.
-Bye. It was nice meeting you.
-Goodbye.
I'll root for you too.
-Bye.
-Bye. Good luck.
-Good night.
-See you in the morning.
-See you.
What about Young-geon?
-There.
-Up there? Okay.
-Good night.
FRIDGE
HANGERS
Good work today, everyone.
LIVING ROOM
-Good night.
TV CABINET
EVERYONE IS SOUND ASLEEP
5:00 A.M.
IN-BEOM AND JUN-YEOP WRITE LETTERS
Let's go.
Let's move our suitcases to the door
and wake Mr. Kian up.
Okay.
Mr. Kian.
We're checking out now.
-You're leaving now?
-Yes, we're going now.
We wrote letters.
-To the others too?
-Yes.
Bye. Take care.
-Thank you. Bye.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
-Please go back to sleep.
Good night.
KNOCKS OUT
THE SNOW IS KNEE-DEEP
What on earth?
It's cold.
It hasn't been that cold, but it is today.
Three days passed by so fast.
It was our last trip
before entering the military,
so I went in happy and thought,
"Let's have a blast one last time."
I got to share this unique experience
with Jun-yeop.
It felt like I'd gone back
to how we played as kids.
I was able to be more honest
and bolder.
It was a perfect and special time.
Even when I'm old,
I think I'll keep replaying this moment.
We should take one last look
before we leave.
Bye, Kian's B&B.
5:30 A.M.
IN-BEOM AND JUN-YEOP CHECK OUT
EVEN AFTER THEY CHECK OUT
IT KEEPS SNOWING
KIAN'S B&B
IT'S BEEN SNOWING HEAVILY FOR 30 HOURS
IN DAEGWALLYEONG
SNOW BUILDUP HAS REACHED 40 CM
DUE TO OVERNIGHT SNOWFALL,
ROADS ARE EXPECTED TO BE ICY
DAY 8
KIAN'S B&B CLOSES IN 1 DAY
KIAN'S B&B
7:30 A.M.
It's so cold.
DEX TRIES PUTTING A SOCK ON
GIVES UP
BLINKING
HE GETS UP IN THE END
Good morning.
-Hello.
GUESTS WAKE UP ONE BY ONE
What time is it?
It's 8:00 a.m.
THE BOSS WAKES UP TOO
-Did you sleep well?
-Yes.
-Hyeon-seo.
-Yes?
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did.
It was so cozy. I liked it.
-He's adorable.
-I know.
THEY TRY TO TURN ON THE LIGHTS
-Hold on.
-Try it this way.
-This won't work.
-I told you that won't work.
Are you playing volleyball?
-Go on.
-Please do it for us.
-Me?
-Yes.
I'm not that good at this.
It's really difficult.
WATCHING
ONE SHOT
ONE KILL
-Olé!
-She did it.
Olé, olé!
-Olé!
-Oh, my gosh.
Olé.
Aren't you leaving today?
We are.
A-JIN AND A-RIN CHECK OUT TODAY
Hey, it's my birthday today.
Can't you leave later?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-Today?
-Today's your birthday?
-Happy birthday to you
SHY
Is it someone's birthday?
Whose is it?
-Whose?
-Whose birthday is it?
-Hyeon-seo's.
-Hyeon-seo's?
-Today?
-Yes, it's today.
-Happy birthday.
-Really?
We should get a cake later.
Right.
Let's go, Seo-young.
Okay, sure.
We'll get going.
THE GUESTS GO ON A TRIP
-Bye.
-Have a nice trip.
See you later.
Have a nice trip!
Happy birthday, Hyeon-seo.
Thank you.
When you come back later, we'll give…
birthday punches.
I've never seen this much snow before.
GUESTS GO OUT
A-JIN AND A-RIN GET READY TO CHECK OUT
Right, the guys wrote letters
for us before leaving.
They wrote letters?
He wrote them with his left hand.
BECAUSE JUN-YEOP HURT HIS RIGHT HAND
They're so nice.
They have kind hearts.
Are you feeling okay?
I feel so worn out, you know?
I can't even work out properly.
Anyway, I'm sad we have to leave soon.
I want to stay a bit longer.
YEON-KOUNG IS SAD THAT IT WILL END
Stay a few more days then.
We'll shoot for a few more days.
Want to do it?
-Thanks for the gesture.
-Yeah?
Even if you don't mean it, thanks.
No, I really feel sad
that we have to part ways.
Why are you suddenly crying?
He's… Kian's crying. Oh, no.
-Don't cry.
-What? Okay.
We have to leave now.
You're leaving?
You're going? I see.
Thank you so much. Where did it go?
-You wrote letters?
-Yes.
-Really?
-Oh, my gosh.
THEY WROTE THEM LAST NIGHT
WE MADE FOND MEMORIES
AND WE WERE HAPPY FOR 3 DAYS
FROM THE CHOI SISTERS
Thank you.
Oh, my.
Your karaoke performance last night
was so cool.
You were the best.
Did you enjoy your stay?
-Yes, we had so much fun.
-Really?
Thanks to you, we had so much fun too.
SAD
But a three-day stay's too short.
-I know.
-Seriously.
We just got close, and you have to leave.
-Have a safe trip.
Be happy.
Okay.
-Be happy too.
-Thank you.
Goodbye.
-Good luck!
KIAN'S B&B
-Let's go.
-I don't want to go.
We'd been so busy with life
before we came here.
Then, we let ourselves go
and had fun at Kian's B&B.
It felt like going to karaoke after exams.
I think this trip was
the happiest moment in my life.
Bye, Kian's B&B.
Bye, Kian's B&B. For real.
A-JIN AND A-RIN CHECK OUT
What now? Should we clean up?
I'm too tired to clean up.
How about we don't do it?
Let's not do it.
There won't be
any new guests today, right?
-There won't be.
-There better not be.
We had too many guests yesterday.
Then,
let's clean and…
Leave the kitchen to me.
I like your energy.
Let's hang in there.
-Okay, let's go!
-Let's go!
Let's keep going!
-Okay!
-It's our last night!
I mean, we clean every day,
but it's always a mess.
Gosh, why is everything…
Boss.
How can you brush your teeth
when we're all cleaning?
Let me just brush my teeth first.
You should be cleaning the floor,
not your teeth.
I'm sorry.
My teeth are also part
of the cleaning area.
They're in the cleaning area here.
Is that so?
CLEANING HARD
THE BOSS IS CLEANING HIS OWN AREA
I haven't washed trays
since I was discharged from the military.
How did you hang these?
But…
why are you hanging them?
We don't have any new guests.
I guess he wanted to do it too.
How did you do this?
HE MANAGES TO HANG ONE
I can't do it anymore.
HE GIVES UP FAST
I wanted to give it a try.
All done!
Good work.
Now that we have one more person,
we finished by 11:00 a.m.
-I know.
-What time did you usually finish before?
After 1:00 p.m.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We finished so fast today.
-What should we eat?
-Let's see.
What does our part-time worker want?
"Korean beef from Daegwallyeong."
Korean beef?
INTERESTED
Do you want meat?
I know it's lunch,
but I'm craving barbecue.
Okay, let's go here.
KOREAN BEEF FOR LUNCH
Let's go!
Let's go.
It just won't stop snowing.
It's so deep.
UP TO ZUHA'S KNEES
It's unbelievable.
I've never seen so much snow.
Is it like 20 or 30 cm of snow?
ABOUT 50 CM
The scenery's amazing.
This is just incredible.
-This is crazy.
-Look at the scenery.
Cows are just out there.
Is it not cold for them?
Wait, I forgot something.
YEON-KOUNG GOES BACK TO GET IT
WASHING HIS FACE WITH SNOW
-You're washing your face?
-Yeah.
For goodness' sake.
THEN HE TASTES THE SNOW
It's just like sherbet.
-Did you eat it?
-Try it.
-You ate it?
-Have you eaten snow before?
-I haven't.
-He's having a bite right now.
-Is this right?
-Have a bite?
JUN-HO HAS A BITE TOO
-Here.
-Thank you.
Have a bite.
ZUHA HAS A BITE TOO
Is it good?
It's like shaved ice.
DEX TRIES IT TOO
It's good.
It seems delicious to me.
-It's shaved ice.
-We could make bingsu.
Right? It'll be like sherbet
if we add flavorings.
-We just need condensed milk.
-Yeah.
-Yeon-koung.
-Yeah?
Taste some of the snow.
Eat it?
Why are you eating snow?
Because it's clean.
I'm good.
Why would you eat snow?
I can't believe I just ate snow.
-Wait, three have to sit in the back.
-Yeah.
Is there enough space?
Dex, you sit in the front.
-Yes.
-Is that okay?
-I'll sit in the middle.
-Thank you.
Since I'm a part-time worker,
Kian's being so thoughtful.
It's so cramped.
-This is so uncomfortable.
-It's so cramped!
It's so cramped.
Could you not push me with your shoulder?
SHOULDER PRESSED DOWN
No, I moved it forward for you.
Your shoulders are quite broad.
Because I was an athlete.
Or I'll move back
and you push me down.
-Like this?
-Yeah.
It's uncomfortable.
Rest yours on mine.
Rest it?
It's so uncomfortable back here.
Jun-ho, I think it's better
to be driving today.
-Sorry, but…
-Sorry, but can you go faster?
Jun-ho, we've traveled comfortably
thanks to you.
-Right.
-Don't mention it.
How has it been lately, Boss?
As time has gone on,
it's gotten better.
-Really?
-Really? Better?
Ever since Smita said that…
You were all bright like light,
but it's off now.
The light's off?
My light is off now?
-You can feel that?
-Yes.
-Right, you've changed.
-You came to your senses.
THE BOSS WOKE UP AFTER THAT
I also thought
you'd changed a lot since then.
And Kazuha's tears.
What? Zuha's tears?
I asked, "Are you having a tough time?"
And then he said, "Zuha, I'm sorry."
Toot!
Wait. I farted then?
NIGHT 3
We're grateful that you joined us.
I mean it.
TOOT
-Sorry.
-Did you fart?
-You farted then.
-You farted then!
Seriously?
That's so lame.
Geez, that's so lame.
Did you check your underwear then?
To see If he pooped?
He'd been wearing the same pair
of underpants for three days already.
I checked.
No wonder why he changed
his underwear after that.
-That's crazy.
-After three days.
Thank you for driving us.
-We're here.
-Thank you.
-This is nice.
It's over after we clean up tomorrow.
CLOSING TOMORROW
I can't believe tomorrow's the last day.
I think I'll miss it.
I've worked you so hard.
-Hello.
-It's here.
I can't believe we're having Korean beef.
Put it on.
-Should we start grilling?
-Sure.
It looks so good.
It won't take long to cook.
-Right.
-Yes.
You can eat it now.
Thank you for the food.
Bon appétit.
Hey, this meat is so good.
-To die for?
-It's insane.
This is so good.
Hey, eat up.
Oh, my.
KIAN FINALLY TRIES SOME
It's so nice to eat out.
Seriously.
What is this?
What is it?
It's not a guest, right?
IT'S THE LAST DAY
BUT NEW GUESTS?
What is this?
-It's a video call.
-A video call?
NERVOUS
Are you entering boot camp?
We're at the training center.
IT'S IN-BEOM AND JUN-YEOP
-It's In-beom.
-He's entering now.
12:50 P.M.
-The parade ground.
-I can't watch.
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
Take care.
-Okay. Wish me luck.
-Okay.
I'll let you talk to everyone.
Hi.
-Hello.
Take care and stay healthy!
-Okay.
Now, Zuha.
They'll be so happy.
-Right.
-Hi.
-It's Kazuha.
-You can do it!
-Let's go, Kazuha!
Hey, guys.
Good luck.
Take care.
-Thank you. Salute!
-Salute!
Salute.
What's it like in there?
Tougher than Kian's B&B?
Of course. Gosh.
Then, do they have to
wash up no matter what?
Is it mandatory?
Do they have to maintain personal hygiene?
Yeah, they have to.
What if you don't want to shower?
-You can't.
-No way.
I'm sure that's against military law.
So did you not learn properly
in the military?
You don't wash yourself often.
-I didn't see that coming at all.
-Right?
When I was in the military,
they kept telling me to shower.
And it did make me hate showering
after I was discharged.
I mean, it's always been a mystery to me.
"Why does he lie in bed
when he's covered in sweat?"
"Why is he putting
his head on the pillow?"
And when you tell me to wash up,
-it reminds me of that trauma.
-Really?
I think I was traumatized by you too.
Because of officers like you,
I became so defiant.
Really?
"Why do they keep telling me
to wash up? I won't!"
"I'll shower when I want to."
So you don't shower much these days?
No, I do shower,
but only when I want to.
CAN'T UNDERSTAND
The smell's not so bad yet.
Tonight's the last night.
Is there anything else you'd like to do?
How about we have dinner outside tonight?
-Outside?
-Yeah.
-I think it's a good idea.
-It'll be romantic.
-We'll make tables.
-We can sit on the snow.
How about we make tables with snow?
I think it'll be nice.
I'll try and design it.
Do you want to make a snowman?
BOSS'S IDEA
MAKE A SNOWMAN FOR DECORATION
Sounds good.
Make the snowman as big as you can.
Just make it as tall as me.
-Make it 192 cm tall. Yeah.
-192 cm tall?
It'll be nice
to do more things with the guests.
Like the campfires we had
when we were young,
we could light up some candles.
We always had that moment
during school trips.
Everyone would cry.
That sounds good.
It's because it'll feel different
to talk while holding candles.
Right, it'll be different.
-The candle thing sounds good.
-Yes.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Thank you for the food!
I wonder if they're having fun.
STAFF RETURNS AFTER LUNCH
KIAN'S B&B
CABLE CAR & SKYWALK
HYUN-SEO, SEONG-BHIN, YUN-WOO
Hello.
BALWANGSAN CABLE CAR
We're up so high.
-It's 1,458 m tall.
-That's impressive.
BALWANGSAN SUMMIT
ELEVATION OF 1,458 M
Elevation means "above sea level."
But sea levels are all different.
So it's mean sea level.
If the sea level rises
due to global warming,
its height would shrink?
That's right.
I hope the clouds pass by soon.
That's how clouds form.
Water vaporizes.
-As it rises, air pressure drops.
-The air expands.
It's fast, so adiabatic expansion happens.
According to thermodynamics,
the internal energy decreases,
causing a temperature drop.
AS ALTITUDE RISES,
SCIENCE TALK GROWS DEEPER
So how it works is…
SKY RANCH
SU-RYEON
It's snowing a lot.
YOUTUBER SU-RYEON
I'm at Sky Ranch now.
It's so pretty.
SKY RANCH
I love it!
I wonder if there are sheep out here.
FINDS A SHEEP TAKING A WALK
It's so cute.
What's its name?
It's Chanel.
Chanel?
Let's go, Chanel.
It's so excited.
You can give the hay and feed
to all the animals.
Thank you. Gosh, it's so cute.
It's Chanel's mukbang.
MEANWHILE, THE ICE CLIMBERS
Let's go.
But where do we go?
"Seonjaryeong Valley."
That's our destination.
IF YOU WALK UP 2 KM FROM SKY RANCH
BAEKDUDAEGAN SEONJARYEONG
ELEVATION OF 1,157 M
SEONJARYEONG VALLEY
Let's go. Follow me.
Is that the right way?
It is.
Right, when will we ever
get to see this much snow again?
The snow's so deep.
It's so heavy.
Hey, clear the path.
PLOWING THROUGH SNOW
This is a workout.
The horses are moving.
They're moving.
This is not easy.
It's getting tough.
Let's take a break.
I don't think I can make it.
GIVES UP GOING TO SEONJARYEONG
You even brought a pickax.
Shall we make it?
We're building our own house.
We'll do some shoveling.
It's more exciting than I thought.
It is.
How's this for a bar table?
HANGING MEDALS TOO
-It's already finished.
-It's our house now.
When will we get to play
like this in the snow again?
This is happiness. What else is there?
Thank you.
THE STAFF RETURN TO KIAN'S B&B
2:30 P.M.
It stopped snowing.
Kian, should we carve into the slope
and make chairs?
If we do it on flat ground,
it'll take forever.
The slope will be better.
We can just have them sit down this way.
HERE
We'll all have to do it together.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Snow shovels.
The snow!
Hey.
KNEE-DEEP
Just this much.
Should we slide down?
GOING DOWN WHILE MAKING A PATH
AN ORDEAL FROM THE BEGINNING
Around here…
Let's make chairs here first.
Here? Facing which direction?
Facing that direction.
-Facing this way?
-That way.
VIEW OF KIAN'S B&B
IN THE MIDDLE OF SNOWY MOUNTAINS
-Here, right?
-Yeah. Dig here.
CONSTRUCTING OUTDOOR RESTAURANT
-Pile it up?
-Pile it up and make chairs.
Dex, should I not dig here?
Dig the front and place it in the back.
WHERE THE CHAIRS WILL BE MADE
Like this. Boom.
-Right.
-Bam!
PLACING AND FLATTENING THE SNOW
-Okay. Bam, bam.
-Bam, bam.
Let's do "bam, bam."
Like this. Bam, bam.
THEY BEGIN FLATTENING THE SNOW
-Zuha, it's "bam, bam."
-"Bam, bam"?
Zuha, have you ever done sapjil before?
"Sapsil"? What's that?
This. Have you done this before?
-No, never.
-Sap means "shovel."
-Sap means "shovel"?
-Yeah, that's right.
-Shovel, for sure?
-Right.
-Shovel, for sure.
-Okay.
That's right.
The work is endless at Kian's B&B.
Goodness.
It's not over until it's over.
I feel so hot.
See how it's hard over here?
If you sit on it…
-It's good.
-It's not bad.
COMFORTABLE
Let me take a seat too.
-It's not falling apart.
-Great.
I'm so comfortable here.
Right? That's your seat.
It's for your long legs.
MATS AS CUSHIONS TO FINISH UP
Let's lay down mats to sit on.
Yes, we need them
or our bottoms will be all wet.
This is awesome.
CHAIRS ARE COMPLETE
Let's make stairs.
STAIRS LEADING TO OUTDOOR RESTAURANT
Like a fancy restaurant.
Dex, did you just make stairs?
-Yes.
-Incredible.
STAIRS ARE COMPLETE
He knows what's needed.
How do I make a snowman?
ZUHA WANTS TO MAKE A SNOWMAN
I've never made a big one before.
What do I do?
SHE MAKES A PILE FIRST
A LARGE PILE
I'll help you.
Isn't the lower part big enough now?
I'll make it bigger.
Bigger?
As big as Yeon-koung.
A SNOWMAN AS TALL AS YEON-KOUNG
It's slowly…
It's slowly getting bigger.
How big should it be?
IT'S AS TALL AS THE BOSS NOW
It's big. It's so big.
Hold on. Can I lift this?
A BIG SNOWBALL?
Move over a bit.
One more.
I can get this up there, right?
Geez! Damn it.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu